# BRIAN ADAMS

brian@brianadams.codes 937.602.8325

Website: <u>brianadams.codes</u>

Github: @badams2527

Current Residence: Cincinnati, OH

# Summary

Educated, efficient, self-motivated software developer with a wide range of past experience in various technologies. Strong communication skills allow for clients and co-workers to pose a problem and get a clear, effective solution in return. Able to gauge a situation from all different angles, and select the proper technology and implementation by not being "tied down" to any single one.

# Education

University of Cincinnati (2012 – 2017)

- Current GPA: 3.469
- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

# Work Experience

Rippe & Kingston Systems, Inc. (October 2013 – Current)

- Co-manage a small team to build and maintain large-scale web applications
- Created development standards guideline for our team to use while developing
- Lead developer on an enterprise contract management application using C#, Vue.js and ASP.NET 4.5
- Utilize the Elastic stack for embedded reporting and searching, along with operational analytics
- Lead developer on a large, scalable reporting application using Python/Flask, RethinkDB, and AngularJS

ENSE (March 2012 - Current)

- Food equipment buying group in the UK
- Sole developer for the company <u>www.enseuk.co.uk</u>
- Design and develop entire web application from the ground up
- Use Node.JS, AngularJS, and RethinkDB to deliver a highly customizable and extensible user experience
- Interact with multiple people in the UK

UC Undergraduate Student Government (April 2015 – April 2016)

- Web Director In charge of all things web-related for Student Government
- Led team of three using Node.JS and MySQL to create a landlord rating and review system
- Use Knockout.js and Sammy.js to create a single page application framework with data-binding

Reynolds and Reynolds (April 2013 – August 2013)

- First professional corporate experience
- Developed internal web applications and WinForms applications using C#, JavaScript, and VB
- Gained experience in version control software (Microsoft Visual SourceSafe and SVN)

## **Activities**

Theta Chi Fraternity (2013 – 2017)

- Founding Father
- Standards Chairman

ACM@UC

# Languages:

- JavaScript
- C#
- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- (

### Software/Frameworks:

- Vue.js
- ASP.NET
- SQL Server
- Elasticsearch
- Logstash
- Kibana
- RabbitMQ
- Node.JS
- AngularJS
- MongoDB
- Flask

### Version Control:

- Git
- Subversion